<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Italia Zone Alert</string>
    <string name="zona_gialla_oneline">Zona Gialla (Yellow Zone)</string>
    <string name="zona_arancione_oneline">Zona Arancione (Orange Zone)</string>
    <string name="zona_rossa_oneline">Zona Rossa (Red Zone)</string>
    <string name="zona_gialla">Zona\nGialla</string>
    <string name="zona_arancione">Zona\nArancione</string>
    <string name="zona_rossa">Zona\nRossa</string>
    <string name="rate">Review on the Play Store</string>
    <string name="with_friend">Share the app with your friends</string>
    <string name="important_note">(*) It should be noted that this section only takes into account measures introduced by national provisions. The Regions and Autonomous Provinces may adopt specific additional restrictive provisions of a local nature, for information on which it is necessary to refer to the institutional information channels of the individual entities.</string>.
    <string name="sharing">Share</string>
    <string name="zona_gialla_text">Allowed to circulate from 5am to 10pm in the same region.\nOnly one visit per day allowed to the home of relatives or friends, for a maximum of 2 people plus children under 14, disabled or non-self-sufficient people cohabitants.\nForbitted to travel from 10pm to 5am and move to other regions, unless there are proven reasons for work, necessity or health.\nReturn to residence, domicile or home always allowed.\n\nCentres and commercial parks closed on holidays and days before holidays. Pharmacies, parapharmacies, health centers, food outlets, tobacconists, newsagents, bookstores, nurseries remain open inside.\n\nActivities in presence at 100% for preschools, elementary and middle schools. At secondary schools, teaching in alternating presence for at least 50% and up to 75% of pupils. Universities open/closed upon autonomous decision, based on the trend of the epidemic.\n\nFilling up to 50% of local public transport, with the exception of dedicated school transport.\n\nConsumption in bars and restaurants allowed from 5 am to 6 pm. From 6 pm to 10 pm allowed only take away of food and drinks from place with kitchen. Home delivery does not have time limits. It is forbidden to consume food and drinks in the streets or parks from 6 to 5 pm.\n\nOpening of museums and exhibitions from Monday to Friday, in compliance with the distance and other preventive measures.\n\nClosed gyms, swimming pools, theaters, cinemas. Sports centers are open.\n\nBetting halls, bingo halls, games rooms and slot machines have been suspended, even in bars and tobacconists.</string>
    <string name="zona_arancione_text">Allowed to circulate from 5 to 22 in the same Municipality. Only one visit per day allowed at the home of relatives or friends, in the same Municipality, for a maximum of 2 people plus children under 14, disabled or non self-sufficient people living together. From municipalities up to 5,000 inhabitants, movements allowed even within 30 km from the borders with prohibition to go to the provincial capitals. Possible to move to other municipalities for work, health or necessity or for services not present in your own municipalities. It is forbidden to circulate from 10pm to 5am, unless proven work, necessity or health reasons. Return to residence, domicile or home is always allowed.\n\nCentres and commercial parks closed on holidays and days before holidays. Pharmacies, parapharmacies, health centers, food outlets, tobacconists, newsagents, bookstores, nurseries remain open inside.\n\nActivities in presence at 100% for preschools, elementary and middle schools. At secondary schools, teaching in alternating presence for at least 50% and up to 75% of pupils. Universities open/closed on autonomous decision, based on the trend of the epidemic.\n\nFilling up to 50% of local public transport vehicles, with the exception of dedicated school transport.\n\nConsumption always prohibited inside of bars and restaurants and in the vicinity. From 5 to 18 allowed to take away food and drinks from all places, from 18 to 22 only from places with kitchens. Home delivery without time limits. It is forbidden to consume food and drinks in the streets or parks from 6 to 5 pm.\n\nMuseums, exhibitions, theaters, cinemas, gyms and swimming pools are closed. Sports centers are open.\n\nBetting halls, bingo halls, games rooms and slot machines have been suspended, even in bars and tobacconists.</string>
    <string name="zona_rossa_text">Allowed to circulate only for work, health or necessity. Only one visit per day allowed at the home of relatives or friends, in the same municipality, for a maximum of 2 people plus children under 14 and disabled or non self-sufficient people living together. From municipalities up to 5,000 inhabitants, visits are allowed even within 30 km from the borders with prohibition to go to the provincial capitals. Return to residence, domicile or home is always allowed.\n\nShops, shopping centers and markets closed. Pharmacies, parapharmacies, health centers, food outlets, tobacconists, newsagents, bookstores, nurseries and other outlets for necessary goods remain open.\n\nOpen barbershops, hairdressers and laundries. Beauty centers closed.\n\nActivities in attendance at 100% for preschools, elementary and middle school. Distance learning at 100% for the other years of middle school and high school. Universities closed, with specific exceptions.\n\nFill up to 50% of local public transport, with the exception of dedicated school transport.\n\nConsumption always prohibited inside bars and restaurants and in the vicinity. From 5 to 18 allowed to take away food and drinks from all places, from 18 to 22 only from places with kitchens. Home delivery without time limits. It is forbidden to consume food and drinks in the streets or parks from 6 to 5 pm.\n\nMuseums, exhibitions, theaters, cinemas, gyms, swimming pools and sports centers are closed Physical activity is allowed near the house and individual sports activities are allowed.\n\nSuspended activities in betting rooms, bingo, game rooms and slot machines also in bars and tobacconists.</string>
    <string name="rule_zone">Rules by color</string>
    <string name="info">About the app</string>
    <string name="copyright">©Copyright 2021 Giancarlo Mennillo</string>
    <string name="loading">Loading…</string>
    <string name="information">©2021 Italia Zone Alert - All rights reserved.\n\nApp Created and developed by Giancarlo\nMennillo.\n\nFor information, problems and suggestions on how to improve the app send a email to:\n\n"giancarlo.mennillo@gmail.com"\n\nor use the button in the menu.\n\nThe map in real time is displayed and updated by using the data of the italian government website in particular the section “Faq sulle misure adottate dal Governo”:\nhttp://www.governo.it/it/articolo/domande-frequenti-sulle-misure-adottate-dal-governo/15638.\n\nThe information regarding the rules based on color is extracted from images published on the facebook page \'\'Palazzo Chigi - Presidenza del Consiglio dei Ministri\'\':\nhttps://www.facebook.com/palazzochigi.it\n\nIt should be noted that the section  \'\'Rules by colour \'\' takes into account exclusively the measures introduced by national provisions. The Regions and Autonomous Provinces may adopt specific further restrictive provisions, of a local nature, for information on which it is necessary to refer to the institutional information channels of the individual bodies.</string>
    <string name="version">App version:</string>
    <string name="actual_zone_rules">Current rules</string>
    <string name="connection_error">Connection error!\nCheck your internet connection and click on retry.</string>
    <string name="retry">Retry</string>
    <string name="fromDate">(From </string>
    <string name="linkUtiliText">Information for Italian citizens returning from abroad and foreign citizens in Italy:\nhttps://www.esteri.it/mae/it/ministero/normativaonline/decreto-iorestoacasa-domande-frequenti/focus-cittadini-italiani-in-rientro-dall-estero-e-cittadini-stranieri-in-italia.html\n\nCurrent rules:\nhttps://www.esteri.it/mae/it/ministero/normativaonline/normativa-altre-amministrazioni.html\n\nFAQ of the Government about travel in Italy:\nhttp://www.governo.it/it/articolo/domande-frequenti-sulle-misure-adottate-dal-governo/15638\n\nWebpage Viaggiare Sicuri for further information about returns:\nhttp://www.viaggiaresicuri.it/</string>
    <string name="links">Useful links</string>
    <string name="infoTitle">Info</string>
    <string name="rules_not_available">No provisions in force at the moment</string>
</resources>

